Narrator: 1
A: Oh look! An Inter Milan football shirt. It’s perfect for Johnny!
B: Yes, good idea. Oh… it’s very expensive.
A: Football shirts are always expensive.
OK. What we can get for Jessica?
B: She likes football, too.
A: Yes, but she never wears football shirts.
What about this bag?
B: I don’t know. Does she like bags?
A: She loves bags…
Narrator: 2
A: Tom, do I need my swimming things?
B: Yes, the hotel’s near the beach.
Can you see my phone charger?
A: Yes, here it is.
Do you want me to put it in the suitcase or in your bag?
B: In my bag, please. Thanks.
Narrator: 3
A: Good morning. How can I help you?
B: Hello, I want a car for three days, please – for today, Tuesday and Wednesday.
A: No problem, what kind of car would you like?
B: A small car is fine. It’s just me.
A: Is a Honda Jazz OK?
B: Yes, great.
A: Can I see your driving licence?
B: Yes, here you are.
Narrator: 4
A: Is that a number 13?
B: Yes. I think it is.
No, it’s a 23.
A: Another 23?
I don’t believe it! That’s the third one. And no 13.
B: Another one’s coming now.
Let’s see. Yes. That’s a 13.
A: At last!